So hello guys my name is Sunil Thakur and
you are watching you are present so in today's
video I will talk about travel
insurance so secondly before that I used to work as an
executive in a travel agency in Shimla and I had
made some contacts there so I get their text messages,
likes and calls saying they have some
problem regarding travel insurance so a
few days ago they had done
Shalaghat restaurant in Kukshi
through a travel agent through which they were coming on this tour
so the travel agents were told
that if you live with pregnancy then
they took this nine back travel insurance so it was
said that if there is
any problem in anything then that
travel insurance will cover it friends so
save them, they get any travel
insurance done so after that
when they went to the store, at that time the beds were lying down
and their vehicles met with an accident
so later they contacted Amazon
that this happened so the travel agent
refused to Pooja saying that we
can give lemon in it  So I
contacted them regarding your message,
I had asked you why you have any
document, whatever is connected, Sandhya also
liked him to destroy the sky
comment is made whether you have any suggestion comment
or not, then they accepted that they have
any such document, that this year I could
not help them, from that time onwards, so that there is no
problem, for that I will make a message
text message video, so in this video I will
tell you that if you should take travel
insurance, then
why should you not take it and
how can you people get it and from where,
if you travel anywhere
in India, you type in your Amla juice or you take
it outside, then you have done the medical
return, then your tourism department has cut it
or pages department, okay, so if you are
travelling to India and here you are travelling outside India, then
you should not be a travel
Aishwarya because it has
many benefits for you, so there
is a button of many things from travel insurance,
if there is a see nearby and it is not set
then travel can do something from it  You
may get some benefit from this, so I will
engage you in this, if you travel somewhere, then
it is better for your travel insurance,
I have
seen many such companies in many matches, which have their own 1 inch
plus camera, you put it on the hotspot, we will
take it for you like this and later if
something like this happens, then they
wash their hands off by saying that Sanwariya products,
so understand that in the case of my plan also, I used to
call them and say that you are
liable to get some good coverage from this, then
you will be covered by them,
but when a person is interested in that service, then
they do not have any lift or comment,
as you
get everything except life insurance or other types, then he
cannot do anything in that because the company
cannot do anything if it refuses to take you away, so
where will you get the travel
insurance, I will tell you about that in this video
and at the same time how can you make this calendar,
I will tell you everything in this video,
so whenever you take travel insurance, then
till this year from a verified company,
if your travel in the island says  It is that whatever you
take from one table spoon, you will
give it to your friends, then that will also be your dal, so if that
meat companies, insurance
companies, murder and blood, that solution will be given to you on
airplane, only then you will get it from us, but youth
is a bundle of those powers and
keep the copy of the insurance with you, if you are
going for your exam or
someone has given you a creative plan for one day,
you will also get the attempt length, that is the situation,
if it is for your skin,
you will get one day leave, one table
spoon will go in the month of Kartik and you will get the
entries in between, then the
big companies provide you the table this year,
some of them would be
Tata, Reliance General Insurance
and along with that, IRCTC and
Indian Railways
provide travel insurance, along with that
policy you can buy it from retail shops in the market
because you get the plans of all the companies there, so
you have no problem in buying the
cheapest and best travel insurance, you
can take it from that whenever you are air travelling  If you have an insurance
policy, you should be very careful about the
points in which you should check the detailed resources
before taking the account. Now,
if you have any policy article, then
you should keep in mind that in it you will
get some medical facilities. If you
sign in while travelling, some incomplete details are left, then you can get it in the
pass
and the second account is this flight
delay, which is done by all the companies.
As you are going on a chafing trip,
if you get late for some work, then you can get an
immediate insurance
here, so you can get some plane
later and along with this,
you have a separate duty, if
you have
some plane nearby, then if you can get that plane, then you can buy an
airplane because
I will tell you in this video. So, if
you are interested in adventure activities or
trekking, gambling and roaming, then you should definitely
go for this medical source because there is no
medicine expense in it, you have almost no
birthday.  270 will charge you 200 paise for
300 rupees.
If you travel a lot, then
you can also buy lemon juice and
this product because
you will get a better deposit in it. So, let's
use it for travels,
you are doing everything else, so how to claim it. So,
I will tell you about the claim process,
like if you
go somewhere by any medical emergency
and you face any medical emergency,
whatever happens to you, you get cured, then
how do you get pregnant?
For this, if you are a
charitable person, then you should not have the
customer care number of that company.
Also, you should not have any policy
number of 14 for 1000 rupees
because on the
same policy, whatever you take,
if you get the tablet immediately, if everything gets
cured, then you will get medical facility
of full expenses.  Your travel
insurance will be taken care of by you, so whenever you feel like it,
first of all you should file an
FIR, after that
you should call your unit and give information about it, I
hope that all of you will be happy and
skiing, so if you do ad travelling then there should
not be any arrangement,
I think it is your wish,
but I will tell you that you should not
believe in it because it
exists directly like a life insurance and a dream, so that's all
in today's video,
if you have any questions, you can
follow me here and also I
can arrest you in my comment, I will
retain your eyes, so I will send you
in the next video, till then thank you.